A truly transformative tale
Tusk is a comedy, horror film directed by Kevin Smith.
When his best friend and podcast co-host goes missing in the backwoods of Canada, a
young guy joins forces with his friend's girlfriend to search for him.
Howard Howe, played by Michael Parks.
Wallace Bryton, played by Justin Long.
Ally Leon, played by Genesis Rodriguez.
Teddy Craft, played by Haley Joel Osment.
Guy Lapointe, played by Johnny Depp.
Border Agent, played by Harley Morenstein.
Tusk is a 2014 American independent black comedy body horror film written and
directed by Kevin Smith, based on a story from his SModcast podcast.
The film stars Michael Parks, Justin Long, Haley
Joel Osment and Genesis Rodriguez.
The film is the first in Smith's planned True North
trilogy, followed by Yoga Hosers (2016).
The film deals with a narcissistic nymphomaniac podcaster (Long) who travels to Canada for an interview, and in the process
meets an eccentric retired sailor (Parks) with dark plans related to his obsession with a walrus named Mr.
Tusk had its world premiere at the 2014 Toronto International Film Festival, before it
was released by A24 on September 19, 2014, and it received mixed reviews.
The film was Smith's first major wide release since Cop Out
(2010), and has since become a minor cult film.
The film explores themes of canada, obsession, interview, deception, walrus.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.